const data = [
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e0f",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Stendhal",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"Octave Mirbeau",
			"Alphonse Daudet",
			"Guy de Maupassant",
		],
		"question": "Which author wrote 'The Charterhouse of Parma'?",
		"tags": ["arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd5b",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Axl Rose",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Bob Dylan", "Leonard Cohen", "Slash"],
		"question": "William Bailey Is The Real Name Of Whch Singer?",
		"tags": ["pseudonyms", "people", "music"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Society & Culture",
		"id": "646339d101d576cfac3aa3c3",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "The Golden Fleece",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"The Trident of Poseidon",
			"The Helm of Darkness",
			"The Scepter of the Gods",
		],
		"question": "In Greek mythology, what did Jason steal from his Uncle Pelias?",
		"tags": ["society_and_culture", "ancient_greece", "mythology"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95103e",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Cm",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["C", "Cu", "Cr"],
		"question": "What is the chemical symbol for curium?",
		"tags": ["chemistry", "science"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "645fcc91541c4d4fc8cf30ae",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Martin Sheen",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Harrison Ford", "Tom Hanks", "Robert De Niro"],
		"question":
			'Which actor played the role of President Josiah Bartlet on "The West Wing"?',
		"tags": ["tv", "film_and_tv", "acting"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Society & Culture",
		"id": "63dd25cc742e43ed64f1f01e",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Hyundai",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Toyota", "Ford", "Honda"],
		"question": "What company owns the motoring brand 'Kia'?",
		"tags": ["society_and_culture", "business", "motoring"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "625e9dcb796f721e95543f2d",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Yellow",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Green", "Black", "Orange"],
		"question": "Which of these colors is included on the flag of Argentina?",
		"tags": ["flags", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "623387b30161109f922aac3e",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Ethiopia ",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Syria", "Egypt", "Azerbaijan"],
		"question": "Which country was previously called Abyssinia?",
		"tags": ["names", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Film & TV",
		"id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95065c",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Timothy Spall",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Paul Newman", "Tobey Maguire", "Dennis Hopper"],
		"question":
			"Which actor has starred in films including The King's Speech and Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events?",
		"tags": ["acting", "film", "people", "film_and_tv"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Society & Culture",
		"id": "6486be6659bc33d1c362f32a",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "The World Trade Organization",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"The World Tourism Organization",
			"The World Television Organization",
			"The World Textile Organization",
		],
		"question": "What does the abbreviation 'WTO' stand for?",
		"tags": ["organizations", "abbreviations", "initials", "society_and_culture"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f95092b",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Republic of the Congo",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Gabon", "Equatorial Guinea", "Rwanda"],
		"question": "Which of these countries borders Central African Republic?",
		"tags": ["geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "623384bc62eaad73716a8c29",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Everest",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Kilimanjaro", "Elbrus", "Denali"],
		"question": "What is the world's highest mountain?",
		"tags": ["mountains", "records", "general_knowledge", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffc3",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Italy",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Croatia", "Austria", "Switzerland"],
		"question": "In Which Country Is Mount Etna?",
		"tags": ["mountains", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95137f",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Gone with the Wind",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"The Fall of the King",
			"All Quiet on the Western Front",
			"A Tale of Two Cities",
		],
		"question": "In which book does 'Scarlett O'Hara' appear?",
		"tags": ["fictitious_characters", "literature", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"id": "62433440cfaae40c12961430",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "A Buck",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["A Ram", "A Billy", "A Boar"],
		"question": "What is a male hamster known as?",
		"tags": ["science"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f9507f5",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Oceania",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["South America", "Europe", "Asia"],
		"question": "The country of Samoa is on which continent?",
		"tags": ["geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffbc",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Athens",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Alexandria", "Corinth", "Sparta"],
		"question": "What is the capital of Greece?",
		"tags": [
			"capital_cities",
			"europe",
			"greece",
			"general_knowledge",
			"geography",
		],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a5b",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Belarus",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Bulgaria", "Lithuania", "Latvia"],
		"question": "Which of these countries borders Ukraine?",
		"tags": ["ukraine", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa2a",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "High Renaissance",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Art Nouveau", "Crystal Cubism", "Baroque"],
		"question":
			'The painting "The Last Supper" by Leonardo da Vinci is a part of which art movement?',
		"tags": ["painting", "art", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "64fb150b717513cb7919038a",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Thousand",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Hundred", "Million", "Few"],
		"question":
			"What is the number missing from the Khaled Hosseini book title: 'A ___ Splendid Suns'?",
		"tags": ["novels", "books", "arts_and_literature", "literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950efb",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"Jack Vance",
			"George R. R. Martin",
			"Robert A. Heinlein",
		],
		"question": "Which author wrote 'Tarzan'?",
		"tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Sport & Leisure",
		"id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950078",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Belgium",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["France", "Italy", "Austria"],
		"question": "Where were the 1920 Olympics held?",
		"tags": ["1920's", "sport", "olympics"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Film & TV",
		"id": "647638d1f05ea6d6f587a152",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Animal House",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"The Breakfast Club",
			"Fast Times at Ridgemont High",
			"The Karate Kid",
		],
		"question":
			"Which 1978 movie features the line 'It was the Deltas against the rules... the rules lost!'?",
		"tags": ["film", "film_and_tv", "film_quotes"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e41",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Mikhail Bulgakov",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Vladimir Nabokov", "Ayn Rand", "Stanis≈Çaw Lem"],
		"question": "Which author wrote 'Heart of a Dog'?",
		"tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe68",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Britney Spears",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Madonna", "Alanis Morissette", "Nicki Minaj"],
		"question":
			"Which American singer, songwriter, dancer and actress released the song '(You Drive Me) Crazy'?",
		"tags": ["songs", "musicians", "music"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"id": "63e13a25106de6ffa7d4a7a1",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Dodecagon",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Octagon", "Hexagon", "Triangle"],
		"question": "What is the name of a shape with twelve sides?",
		"tags": ["science", "mathematics", "shapes"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd82",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Paul McCartney",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Janet Jackson", "Jon Bon Jovi", "Sting"],
		"question": 'Who Sang With Michael Jackson On "Say Say Say"?',
		"tags": ["people", "music"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"id": "645c9f8642ea81e2554c5f2e",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Apiology",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Entomology", "Ornithology", "Zoology"],
		"question": "What is the study of bees called?",
		"tags": ["animals", "science"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Society & Culture",
		"id": "6293ecdc7f41d6338b96ef10",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Zoroaster",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"Antoine Laurent Lavoisier",
			"James Watt",
			"St. Augustine",
		],
		"question": "Which influential historical person was a religious prophet?",
		"tags": ["people", "history", "society_and_culture", "religion"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "6237353fcfe13103f55eb512",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "India",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["United Kingdom", "Indonesia", "Ireland"],
		"question":
			"Which region of the world uses '.in' at the end of its web addresses?",
		"tags": ["the_internet", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "General Knowledge",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc71",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Lackadaisical",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Yarborough", "Curmudgeon", "Ratoon"],
		"question": "Which word is defined as 'lacking enthusiasm or determination'?",
		"tags": ["words", "general_knowledge"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "General Knowledge",
		"id": "647638daf05ea6d6f587a167",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "B",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["C", "D", "E"],
		"question":
			"What middle initial is shared by film director Cecil DeMille and basketball star Kobe Bryant?",
		"tags": ["directors", "names", "people", "sport"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"id": "6486be3159bc33d1c362f31a",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Paul Simon",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Elton John", "Billy Joel", "Bob Dylan"],
		"question":
			"Who won the Grammy Song of the Year award in 1970 for the song 'Bridge Over Troubled Water'?",
		"tags": ["music", "songs"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f16",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Alice Munro",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Ivan Turgenev", "E. T. A. Hoffmann", "Alphonse Daudet"],
		"question": "Which author wrote 'Friend of My Youth'?",
		"tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdfc",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Samoa ",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Tonga", "Vanuatu", "Tuvalu"],
		"question":
			"Which Pacific Nation Gained Independence From New Zealand In 1962?",
		"tags": ["countries", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "History",
		"id": "639895855c9a75021f31045e",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "The Montgolfier Brothers",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"The Wright Brothers",
			"The Vespucci Brothers",
			"The Orville Brothers",
		],
		"question": "Who invented the hot air balloon in the 18th century?",
		"tags": ["history", "1700's", "inventions", "aviation"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f968",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Pale Fire",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Portnoy's Complaint", "The Tin Drum", "The Swimmer"],
		"question": "Which book contains the character 'Charles Kinbote'?",
		"tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f38",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "J. R. R. Tolkien",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["G. K. Chesterton", "Philip Pullman", "C. S. Lewis"],
		"question": "Which author wrote 'The War of the Jewels'?",
		"tags": ["arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "General Knowledge",
		"id": "6355b7e4e8b368eed3a68234",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "plosive",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["nasal", "approximant", "fricative"],
		"question":
			"In phonetics, the b in 'boat' is an example of what kind of sound?",
		"tags": ["language", "linguistics", "general_knowledge", "science"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b7e",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Destiny's Child",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["TLC", "All Saints", "Spice Girls"],
		"question": "Which band did Beyonc√© start her career with?",
		"tags": ["general_knowledge", "people", "music", "bands"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "6233862d62eaad73716a8cba",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Moscow",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Belgrade", "Budapest", "Odessa"],
		"question": "Where is Gorky Park?",
		"tags": ["tourist_attractions", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9512e4",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Pablo",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Gavroche", "Didi", "Pedro"],
		"question":
			"What was the first name of the Spanish modernist and cubist painter Picasso?",
		"tags": [
			"arts_and_literature",
			"people",
			"names",
			"art",
			"general_knowledge",
			"painting",
		],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Arts & Literature",
		"id": "6497ef4d0752843c0d8aadd7",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "The Wind in the Willows",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"Alice's Adventures in Wonderland",
			"The Cat in the Hat",
			"Charlotte's Web",
		],
		"question":
			"Which novel contains the line \"'Toad Hall,' said the Toad proudly, 'is an eligible self-contained gentleman's residence'\"?",
		"tags": ["quotes", "literature", "novels", "arts_and_literature"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Society & Culture",
		"id": "649dee4e615f8db40f5422d6",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Wednesday",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Thursday", "Friday", "Saturday"],
		"question": "What day follows 'Ash' in the name of the first day of Lent?",
		"tags": ["society_and_culture", "dates"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "History",
		"id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f952273",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "The Bible",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Don Quixote", "The Magna Carta", "Macbeth"],
		"question":
			"In 1447, Johannes Gutenberg invented the printing press. What was the first book he produced?",
		"tags": ["history"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Film & TV",
		"id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb7d",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "All Quiet on the Western Front",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["The Big House", "Disraeli", "The Divorcee"],
		"question": "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1930?",
		"tags": ["academy_awards", "film", "film_and_tv"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"id": "6233845762eaad73716a8c01",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "Aegean Airlines",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["Olympus Air", "Hermes", "Hellenic Airways"],
		"question": "What Is The National Airline Of Greece?",
		"tags": ["business", "europe", "geography"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c31",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "ABBA",
		"incorrectAnswers": ["In Flames", "HammerFall", "Katatonia"],
		"question":
			"Which Swedish pop group released the song 'The Winner Takes It All'?",
		"tags": ["music"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950505",
		"idcorrectAnswer": "waves or wave motions",
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			"weather",
			"Tibet",
			"mental processes in living creatures",
		],
		"question": "What is Kymatology the study of?",
		"tags": ["words", "science"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
	{
		"category": "Film & TV",
		"id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc24",
		"idcorrectAnswer": '"I see dead people."',
		"incorrectAnswers": [
			'"I have had it with these mother‚Äî‚Äî snakes on this mother‚Äî‚Äî plane!"',
			'"I have nipples Greg. Could you milk me?"',
			'"You talking to me?"',
		],
		"question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Sixth Sense'?",
		"tags": ["quotes", "film", "general_knowledge", "film_and_tv"],
		"type": "Multiple Choice",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"regions": [],
		"isNiche": false,
	},
];



class Results {
  getQuestions() {
    return data;
  }
}